[
    {
        "question": "1) What is Xamarin?",
        "answer": "Xamarin is a company that builds the software. The main operation of Xamarin is to build mobile apps that work on cross-platforms. It is used to build the UI for Android, iOS, and Windows operating system. Xamarin application shares the codebase. Xamarin's feature is similar to the native application. A developer can download the Xamarin tools in Visual Studio.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "2) What is the advantage of Xamarin Development?",
        "answer": "Benefits of Xamarin Development are:\nADVERTISEMENT\nADVERTISEMENT\nThe user interface is simple and native.\nDevelopers can use Xamarin to make cross-platform apps.\nThe chances of the bugs are less.\nWe can create an app for iOS, Android, and Windows using the same codebase.\nXamarin has powerful community support.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "3) What are the disadvantages of Xamarin Development?",
        "answer": "Disadvantages of Xamarin app Development are:\nThe development of user interfaces in Xamarin is Time-Consuming.\nThe apps created in Xamarin have a large file size. These apps are mostly between the 3 MB to 15 MB in size in the store.\nEven apps share the code across the platform, but there is also a need for the developer to create the linkage in the OS, which is difficult for the user.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "4) What are the development approaches in Xamarin?",
        "answer": "Xamarin has two approaches for app development. These are\nXamarin.Forms: Forms are the choices for the developers who want to create one application for all the separate mobile platforms, which are Windows, iOS, and Android.\nXamarin Native: This approach is used in those scenarios when we want to create a separate version of the same App for different platforms. Developers can use Xamarin.iOS, Xamarin.Android and Xamarin.Windows libraries to create the applications for each particular platform.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms?",
        "answer": "The differences between the Xamarin and Xamarin.Forms are:\nXamarin Xamarin.Forms\nXamarin is an app development tool to create cross-platform mobile applications. Xamarin.Forms is a UI toolkit to develop the application.\nDevelopers can use Xamarin.iOS, Xamarin.Android and Xamarin.Windows to create the application which is based on the particular platform for which the apps are created. Developers can use Xamarin. Forms to create the one native version of the App which can run the entire mobile platform.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "6) What is Xamarin Profiler?",
        "answer": "Xamarin Profiler is a tool which is used by the developers to keep an eye on the information about the particular App inside the Visual Studio. With the help of Xamarin Profiler, developers can easily analyze the App's behavior. We can use the profiler to track the application's memory information and can sample its statistics.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "7) What is Xamarin Insights?",
        "answer": "Xamarin insight is a tool that allowed the developers to identify and track the issue with the apps in real-time. We can also use this for the monitoring system to report the problems. Xamarin introduced Xamarin Insight in October 2014. However, it was closed on March 31, 2016. In today's time, developers can believe in Visual Studio App Center for the same functionality that is provided by the Xamarin Insights.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms?",
        "answer": "Xamarin.Forms is a framework which is used to build the user interface in the mobile application. In the same codebase, developers have to write the UI separately for each platform. This is time consuming and difficult process. Xamarin.Forms allows the developer to create just one UI which can be used across all platforms like Android, iOS, and Windows.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "9) Which programming language supports the Xamarin?",
        "answer": "Xamarin supports three languages in the development of mobile applications:\n\n\nC#\nF#\nVisual Basic.NET",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "10) What is the role of XAML in Xamarin?",
        "answer": "XAML or Extensible Markup Language is a special tool that allows the developer to define the user interface in Xamarin app development. XAML has a vital role in Xamarin, but it is not necessary for app development in Xamarin.Forms. Xaml works with ModelView-ViewModel or MVVM architecture of an application.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "11) What is Xamarin Studio?",
        "answer": "Xamarin Studio is a standalone IDE for developing the cross-platform mobile application, which is based on the open-source project Monodevelop.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "12) What are the differences between the Xamarin Studio and Visual Studio?",
        "answer": "Both Xamarin Studio and Visual Studio are IDEs used to develop the Android, iOS, Class Library, Console, PCL, and Windows Phone application. Both Xamarin Studio and Visual Studio support F#.\nXamarin Studio Visual Studio\nXamarin Studio works on both Windows OS X environments. Visual Studio is available only for the windows environment.\nOn Windows, Xamarin Studio doesn't support windows phone and iOS project. In Visual Studio, we can create any app.\nXamarin Studio on Windows supports only Xamarin.Android project. Visual Studio supports Xamarin.Android, Xamarin.iOS, and Xamarin.Windows project.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms apps?",
        "answer": "Xamarin.Forms is a platform to develop the cross-platform mobile applications by using the XAML for Front-End and C# for the backend of the application. In Xamarin.Forms application, we can share all code. Xamarin.Forms also give the 100% API coverage of Android and iOS native APIs. So that, we can develop native Android, iOS, and Windows apps.\nFor more information about the LifeCycle of the Xamarin.Forms, click on this link: Xamarin LifeCycle\nWhen we create Xamarin.Forms application we will see four projects:\nPortable Project: This is the project where we will write 95% of our application code, and this code is shared in all the three platforms.\nAndroid: This is the project where we set the Android application icon and splash screen, and all the other code will come from the portable project.\niOS: In this project, we set the iOS application architecture and icon.\nUniversal Windows: Universal Windows Platform is the application platform",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "14) What are the types of data binding modes in Xamarin?",
        "answer": "The different types of data binding modes are:\nDefault\nOne way: changes in the source affect the target\nTwo way: Changes in the source and destination affect each other",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "15) What is the difference between the Xamarin and Mono?",
        "answer": "Xamarin Mono\nXamarin is a powerful solution for building awesome apps. Mono is used in those cases when we want to build an app for a single platform. In that case, there is a need for a Native platform.\nWith the help of Xamarin, we can create Native apps for multiple platforms via the same IDE, APIs, and Language. Native mobile apps are built on Android, iOS.Java, and Windows.\nUsing Xamarin, we can skip the extra development time for each platform. Using Mono, we cannot skip the extra development time for each platform.\nXamarin apps are accessible for more comprehensive ranges at a lower cost. Mono apps are accessible for the broader ranges at a higher cost.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms?",
        "answer": "The following are the different types of scenarios that are used in Xamarin.Forms:\nView to View binding\nBackward binding\nBinding with the models\nBinding with the collections",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "17) What is data binding in Xamarin?",
        "answer": "Data Binding is a technique that is used to synchronize the source of the data with the user interface. When the data binding is done and the data or our business model changes, then it shows the changes automatically to the UI elements and vice versa.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "18) What is the Xamarin test cloud?",
        "answer": "The Xamarin test cloud allows us to test the mobile application on various devices. The Test cloud is also used for automated testing in many real devices simultaneously.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "19) How to set up the Xamarin?",
        "answer": "For Xamarin set up, there are four steps:\nDownload the Xamarin Installer\nRun the installer\nConfigure it\nActivation of Xamarin\nFor more information click here: Installation of Xamarin",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms?",
        "answer": "Different types of layout control in Xamarin.Forms are:\nStack Layout\nContentView\nFrame\nScrollView\nTemplateView\nAbsolute Layout\nGrid\nRelative Layout\nFor more information about layout click on this link: XamarinLayout",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms?",
        "answer": "The different types of pages present in the Xamarin.Forms are:\nContent page- This type of page displays a single view, often a container such as a stack layout or the scroll view.\nMasterDetail page- MasterDetailPage is a page that manages the information between the two related pages.\nNavigation Page- Navigation page manages the navigation of the pages.\nTabbed Page- Tabbed Page helps the navigation of the children page using the tab.\nTemplate Page- The Template page helps to display the content of the full page with a control template.\nCarousal Page- This page allows the swipe gesture between the subpages, such as a gallery.\n\nFor more information about the Xamarin Page, click on this link: Xamarin.Forms",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "22) What are the advantages of Xamarin?",
        "answer": "Benefits of Xamarin are:\nWe can deliver the native iOS, Android, and Windows app using the existing skills, and code (C#, XAML).\nWe can take full advantage of Native APIs with Xamarin Technology.\nXamarin Component Store allows us to add the high-quality components to our App directly from IDE, including controls, web service APIs, and more.\nPCL/shared project makes the development easy for developers to share the same code base across different projects.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms?",
        "answer": "There are two methods of sharing the code between the cross-platform applications:\nPortable Libraries (PCL)\nShared Projects\n\nThe goal of the code-sharing strategy is to support the architecture where multiple platforms can utilize a single code base.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "24) What is the difference between the portable class library and shared projects?",
        "answer": "Portable Class Library\n\n\nWe create Class Library in .Net to reuse our code or to make our code reusable with the same type of application only, but that might not work for some conditions. Here we assume, we have created the class library for WPF or any other kind of application. And if we want to access the same type of class library for Windows 8 or Windows phone application, then in this scenario, we can't refer this as a class library.\nWe want the same application for all the platforms to make our life easy. We want the same application used on multiple platforms. Microsoft technology is growing day by day, and it covers every device. All types of applications we can build and validate within one framework on all types of platform Windows, Web, Mobile, or Tab.\nPCL solves this problem. .Net 4.5 introduced the Portable Class Library (PCL) for developing the business logic in one location, and we can use this library end to end in all types of applications or all platforms (Windows, web, or Mobile) on .Net Framework.\nThe figure shows the flow of the Portable Class Library (PCL). All these applications run on the .Net Framework. All these applications have different environments and platforms, but they all can easily use the Portable Class Library. In other words, we can say that we only need to prepare the UI and do the DataBinding of our application for all the windows, web and mobile, because the same business logic can then use the entire platform.\nShared Project\nA shared project is a project that contains standard code and linked to each specific platform library or App. It is compiled as a part of the platform-specific code. To develop a nice solution that is based on a shared project, there is a need to architect it to have the core features in the shared project. Here possibly, we may use partial classes, abstract classes, and interfaces to manage the objects which are specific for each platform in the platform-specific project. These kinds of projects are good when we are in a prototype phase because it is fast to implement the shareable project for the common code. We can use all the advantages of the platform-specific Framework.\n\nShared Code can be branched base on the platform using compiler directive (e.g. #if_Android_,#if_iOS_,#if_Windows_Phone_App.etc.)\nNo output assembly\nRefactoring operations, not update automatically.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "25) What are the advantages of XAML?",
        "answer": "The advantages of XAML are:\nXAML gives a clean division of the application and its code. Thus, it enables a clear developer-design flow.\nXAML is more crisp and precise than a similar code.\nXAML has the parent-child hierarchy of user-interface objects with greater visual interface simplicity",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "26) What are the Views?",
        "answer": "Views are known as control of widgets. They can be visual objects such as Label, Button, Entry, BoxView, ListView, TableView, etc. All the UI elements are the sub-classes of view.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "27) What is the difference between ListView And TableView?",
        "answer": "ListView and TableView controls are similar. We can take them as a single control. The major difference between them is how they layout the items.\nListView: ListView control displays the stacks of data vertically. It is just like a standard Listbox. We use this control to display the order of data in the list, especially the long list, that requires scrolling, like a list of email messages, a list of contacts, or search results.\nTableView: TableView displays the stacks of data horizontally in rows. We use this control when we need more space for rich visualization of the item to be displayed.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "28) What are the types of the App which use Xamarin?",
        "answer": "The different types of apps which use the Xamarin are:\nOLO- an online platform to order food.\nThe World Bank survey app- This App is used for the global survey.\nStoryo- This App helps to create videos from the picture.\nFreshdirect- This App is our friendly grocer.\nJust Giving- a philanthropic interface.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms?",
        "answer": "The scenario used by the Xamarin.Forms are:\nView to view binding\nBackward bindings\nBinding with the collections\nBinding with the models",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "30) What are the apps designed by Xamarin for Android?",
        "answer": "The apps designed by Xamarin for Android are:\nThe secret society\nParental Access\nToolwiz cleaner\niLearnForKids\nGoal 2014 Football manager",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "31) Name the apps that were designed by Xamarin for iOS?",
        "answer": "The apps that were designed by Xamarin for iOS are:\nQuickPLan- Project Plan HD\nNewsPager\nApocalyspe Archer: Zombie invasion\nStone Skimmer: Skimming action game",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Android applications work?",
        "answer": "Xamarin.Android applications depend on Microsoft's Mono Virtual Machine. Mono is Microsoft's open-source implementation of the .Net Framework, which is based on open source standards of C# and CLR. Mono was launched in the year 2001. It was created to allow the .Net applications to work on the Linux platform, but was later modified to support the development on various devices, including embedded systems.\nIn Xamarin, Mono works in parallel with Android's ART. On Android, most of the system facilities like Audio, Graphics, OpenGL, and Telephony are not available directly to the native applications. They can be added through the Android Runtime Java APIs, which is available in one of the Java.*namespaces or the Android.*namespaces. The native applications then interact with the exposed .NET APIs. These APIs then, through the Android Binding, call the Android runtime Java APIs.\nThe architecture looks like this:",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "33) What is Fresh MVVM?",
        "answer": "Fresh MVVM is a super light MVVM framework which is designed specifically for Xamarin.Forms only. Its design is easy, simple, and flexible. It is easy to learn and uses the convention over configuration.\nFresh MVVM is a little different from MVVM. FreshMvvm uses the concept of Page and PageModel instead of View and ViewModel.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "34) What is the difference between the MVVM Cross and MVVM Light?",
        "answer": "MVVM Cross: MVVM Cross is a .NET cross-platform MVVM framework. It allows us to make a cross-platform solution for platforms such as Xamarin. Forms, Xamarin.Android, Xamarin.iOS, Xamarin.Mac and WPF. It is an inactive state of development.\nMVVM Cross requires the application to be divided into two parts: Core and the UI.\nThe Core part contains the View Models, Service, Models, and the Business logic, whereas the UI part consists of the different views and platform-specific code that interact with the core. The views are the View Screens, which contain the graphical content. In addition to Core and UI, the application may contain additional libraries for various functionalities.\nFeatures that are provided by MVVM Cross are:\nAn MVVM architecture pattern\nA flexible Navigation system\nData binding to allow automatic binding with the source to target.\nPlatform-specific support\nInversion of Control Container\nDependency Injection engine\nConsequences of MVVM Cross are:\nIt has an excessive learning curve and lacks a Wiki for how to get started developing the apps.\nMVVM Light: MVVM Light is another Framework that allows the creation of Enterprise-Grade apps using the MVVM Architectural pattern on Xamarin. MVVM Light enables the developer to create and develop MVVM applications on a variety of platforms like Xamarin. Forms, Xamarin.Android, Xamarin.iOS, UWP, and WPF. It allows us to separate the View from Model and hence write the testable and extensible applications. It does not support async.\nMVVM Light application is divided into the following parts:\nView: It is a platform-specific user interface which is associated with the screen.\nViewModel: It exposes the data and related properties of the data.\nViewModel Locator: It registers custom ViewModels.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "35) What is the need of the Model-View-ViewModel (MVVM ) pattern in Xamarin?",
        "answer": "The Model-View-ViewModel can be used on all platforms. It intends to provide a clean separation between the user interface controls and their logic.\n\nBenefits:\nDuring the development process, developers and designers can work independently on their components. Designers can concentrate on the view, and if they are using Expression Blend, they can generate sample data. On the other hand, developers can work on the view model and model components.\nDevelopers create the unit tests for the view model and can create the model for the view.\nIt is easy to redesign the UI of the application without touching the code because the view is implemented entirely in XAML. A new version of the view should work with the existing view model.\nIf there is any existing representation of the model that binds the existing business logic, this can be difficult or risky to change. In this scenario, the view model acts as an adapter for the model classes and enable us to avoid making any major changes to the code of the model.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "36) What is NuGet and how this can be useful in App development?",
        "answer": "NuGet is the most popular package manager for the development in .Net. It is present in Xamarin Studio 5 and Visual Studio. We can easily search and add package/third party libraries to the Xamarin.Forms using IDE.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "37) What is the HTTP client?",
        "answer": "HTTPClient helps the developers to connect with the external world through the internet using the REST-based services. HTTPClient class is used for sending the HTTP requests and receiving HTTP response from a resource, which is identified by URI. HTTPClient class present in System.Net.HTTP namespace.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "38) What is ResourceDictionary?",
        "answer": "ResourceDictionary is used to define the XAML Resources, which can be reused more than once throughout the Xamarin.Forms application.\nXaml Resources are the definition of objects which can be used more than once.\nResourceDictionary allows all the resource objects declared at one place.\nWe can define Styles, ControlTemplates, DataTemplates, Colors, and Converters into the ResourceDictionary.\nIn XAML, resources can be accessed at the Element level (inside specific element), Page (inside page) level or Application Level (inside App.Xaml).",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms and Xamarin Native?",
        "answer": "Xamarin.Forms :\nXamarin.Forms are used when:\nthe requirement of the code is less in the platform-specific scenario.\nCode-sharing is more important than custom UI.\nThe UI is not complex.\nXamarin Native:\nXamarin Native is used when:\na lot of platform-specific code is required.\nCustom UI is more important than code sharing.\nWhen platform-specific APIs are used.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "cs class?",
        "answer": "App.cs is the main class of the App which offers features like:\nMainPage: It helps us to set the initial page of the App.\nProperties Dictionary: It helps us to store the values across the state of the lifecycle.\nStatic Current Property: It gives the instance of the current application object",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "Forms App?",
        "answer": "Lifecycle methods are the set of techniques which are executed when the application enters into a specific state. The ways are:\nOnStart: This method will run when the application starts from the beginning.\nOnSleep: This method will execute when the application goes into the background.\nOnResume: This method will execute when the application comes in the foreground from the sleeping state.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "42) What is the purpose of XAML compiler (XALC)?",
        "answer": "Using the XAML compiler, we can directly compile XAMLs into intermediate (IL) language.\nBenefits:\nIt performs the compile-time checking to find the error in XAML. At compile time it notifies the user about any mistake.\nIt removes the overheads and initialization time for XAML elements.\nIt doesn't include the XAML file into the final assembly, and thus it reduces the assembly time.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "43) What is XAML namespace declaration?",
        "answer": "XAML namespace is the declaration of the namespaces on top of the XAML file. There are two declarations available within the root element when we create any new XAML UI. Here is the default declaration of the xmlns without any prefix:\nxmlns=\"http://xamarin.com/schemas/2014/forms\"  \nThe second declaration uses the x prefix:\nxmlns:x=\"http://schemas.microsoft.com/winfx/2009/xaml\"  \nAll declaration of the namespace which uses the prefix is a non-default declaration.\nSuppose we want to bind the ViewModel with XAML and that ViewModel is declared inside the namespace, \"XamSample.ViewModels\".\nxmlns:vm=\"clr-namespace:XamSample.ViewModels; assembly=XamSample.ViewModels\"  \nThen we can access the element from inside this namespace using VM prefix.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "44) What is the way of navigation from one page to another?",
        "answer": "After clicking on the button of the first page, we call the following method through which we can navigate from one page to another page.\nawait Navigation.PushAsync(new MySecondPageXaml(), true);  \nWe have to use the \"Navigation\" page property which is available under the ContentPage class. This code is written in the coding page of the MainPage.XAML file.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "45) What is ViewCell?",
        "answer": "A ViewCell is a small individual element which represents a single item of the ListView or Table. A ViewCell is not a visual element, but it is a description of the template which creates the visual aspect.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "46) What are the types of Built-in cells?",
        "answer": "The types of built-in cells are:\nTextCell: It is a cell that consists a Title/Primary text and a Detail/Secondary text label.\nImageCell: It is a text cell which includes the image component in the left.\nSwitchCell: This cell contains Label and the toggle switch.\nEntryCell: This cell contains the Label and single line of textbox which can be used to enter the data.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "47) What is the difference between ControlTemplate and DataTemplate?",
        "answer": "ControlTemplate: This template decides how the control should look. It defines the representation style for control.\nFor example, A Button can contain Image and Text.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "48) What are the triggers? How many types of triggers are available?",
        "answer": "Triggers allow us to declare actions in XAML, which changes the appearance of the control when specific condition met for a particular property of the control.\nWe can add triggers at control-level, page-level, or application-level in the resource dictionary. Here are the four types of triggers available. These are:\nProperty Trigger: This trigger executes when the property of the control set a particular value.\nData Trigger: This trigger is similar to a property trigger, but it uses the data binding.\nEvent Trigger: This trigger occurs when an event occurs on the control.\nMulti Trigger: This trigger allows us to set the conditions of multiple triggers before the action occurs.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "49) What is hockey app?",
        "answer": "Hockeyapp offers the testing service for iOS, Android, and Windows phone.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "50) What is TestFlight?",
        "answer": "Apple is the owner of the TestFlight. This is the primary way of the beta test of our Xamarin.iOS apps.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    },
    {
        "question": "51) What are the types to create the Xamarin applications?",
        "answer": "Here, are the three ways to build the apps in Xmarin.\nXamarin.Forms  \nXamarin.Android  \nXamarin.iOS.",
        "reference": "javatpoint.com",
        "role": "xamarin"
    }
]